Guide to the Peter S. Craig Papers, 1904-1983 MS2066
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Reports and studies, 1904-1984; Series 1; 25 Linear Feet
  - Reports and studies, 1965-1969; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Reports and studies, 1970-1976; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Reports and studies, 1966-1983; Series 1 (Box 23)
  - Reports and studies, 1978-1980; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Rock Creek Park hearings, 1955; Series 1 (Box 52, Binder 2)
  - Secretary Boyd's Briefing Book, 1968; series 1 (Box 25, Binder 3)
  - Six-Year Highway Plans, 1964-1965; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - South Leg Freeway (I-695), 1972; Series 1 (Box 35, Binder 2)
  - South Leg Freeway (I-695), 1973; Series 1 (Box 65, Binder 1)
  - Speeches by C. Darwin Stolzenbach, 1961-1963; series 1 (Box 24, Binder 3)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1960; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 2)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1961; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 3)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1962; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 4)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1963; Series 1 (Box 40, Binder 5)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1964; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 5)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1964-1965; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 6)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1966; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 7)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1965; Series 1 (Box 40, Binder 6)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1966-1967; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 8)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1968-1970; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 9)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1971-1972; Series 1 (Box 40, Binder 1)
  - Studies on transportation planning by Peter S. Craig, 1972-1975; Series 1 (Box 40, Binder 2)
  - Tables, 1960-1965; Series 1 (Box 42, Binder 1)
  - Technical Procedures Employed in the Travel Forecast, Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Study, 1965; Series 1 (Box 1, Volume 4)
  - Three Sisters Bridge, 1972; Series 1 (Box 1, Binder 3)
  - Three Sisters Bridge and Route 70-S, 1959-1968; Series 1 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Three Sisters hearings, 1960-1962; series 1 (Box 24, Binder 2)
  - Traffic -- CBD Cordon, undated; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Traffic -- Cordon Line Studies, undated; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Traffic -- DC Line Cordon, undated; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Traffic forecast -- MTS, undated; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Traffic forecast -- NCTA, 1963; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Traffic forecast -- WMATS, 1965; Series 1 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Traffic -- Monthly counts, 1956-1967; Series 1 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Traffic reports, 1963-1966; Series 1 (Box 29, Binder 2)
  - Transfer of DC highway funds, 1975-1976; Series 1 (Box 29, Binder 8)
  - Transit legislation, 1963; series 1 (Box 25, Binder 5)
  - Transportation Plan, National Capital Region, 1959; Series 1 (Box 69, Volume 4)
  - Transportation Planning Board Prospectus, 1965; Series 1 (Box 45, Binder 2)
  - Transportation Study, 1925; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Transportation Survey, 1944; Series 1 (Box 41, Volume 5)
  - Tydings Parking Bill, 1966; Series 1 (Box 33, Binder 1)
  - An Underground Parking Garage Beneath Farragut Square, 1961; Series 1 (Box 66, Volume 5)
  - Union Square diagrams -- Olmsted, Frederick Law, undated; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Vehicle volume summaries, 1966-1971; Series 1 (Box 47, Binder 5)
  - Washington Metropolitan Transportation Study, 1952; Series 1 (Box 67, Volume 4)
  - What Freeways Mean to Your City, 1964; Series 1 (Box 67, Volume 1)
  - Wisconsin Corridor Study, 1972; Series 1 (Box 34, Binder 4)
  - WMATA 1990 forecast, 1967; Series 1 (Box 47, Binder 6)
  - WMATA specifications, Section A-2 Connecticut Avenue Route, 1969; Series 1 (Box 13, Binder 2)
  - WMATA Traffic, Revenue, and Operating Costs, 1969; Series 1 (Box 70, Volume 1)
  - Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Study (WMATS) Reports, 1963-1965; Series 1 (Box 33, Binder 2)
  - Zoning, 1955-1961; Series 1 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Zoning issues, 1971-1973; Series 1 (Box 15, Binder 2)
  - Zoning regulations, 1958-1972; Series 1 (Box 15, Binder 1)
  - Zoning Commission Procedural Regulations, 1972; Series 1 (Box 37, Binder 4)
- Correspondence and memos, 1927-1973; Series 2; 4 Linear Feet
  This series contains incoming and outgoing correspondence and memos from Peter S. Craig, arranged by topic or organization. The material dates from 1927 to 1973, and documents the work done by Craig and related individuals and institutions in opposition to freeway construction in Washington, DC. There is significant material from his work as a committee member of Committee of 100 on the Federal City, as well as his work with the Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning. In addition, the series contains 16 folders of correspondence belonging to Jackson Graham, General Manager of the Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Authority.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic or organization.
  - American Automobile Association, undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - American Red Cross -- E Street Expressway, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Bureau of Public Roads, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Citizens Associations, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Citizens Committee on Homes and Highways, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Civic associations and local groups, undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City -- correspondence, 1960-1961; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder data_value_missing_244251db7aa1f551618e2838658c28b6)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City -- correspondence, 1962; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City -- correspondence [1 of 2], 1963-1964; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City -- correspondence [2 of 2], 1963-1964; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City -- correspondence, 1965-1967; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Committee of 100 on the Federal City -- correspondence, 1973; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Urban Conservation, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Congress -- correspondence (transportation), undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Congressional (general), undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Consultants, undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - DC Highway Law Memo, undated; Series 2 (Box 45, Binder 1)
  - DC recreation, 1940-1941; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Downtown Progress, 1964-1968; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Engineer Commissioner and DC Highway Department, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Federal City Council, 1964-1967; Series 2 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Federal City Council, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Foxhall Village, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Freeway lawsuits, 1966-1967; Series 2 (Box 29, Binder 5)
  - Georgetown Civic Groups, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1967 March-December; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1968 January-June; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1968 July-December; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1969 January-June; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1969 July-December; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1970 January-June; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1970 July-December; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1971 January-March; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1971 April-June; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1971 July-September; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1971 October-December; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1972 January-March; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1972 March-June; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1972 July-September; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1972 October-December; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Graham, Jackson -- correspondence, 1973 January-March; Series 2 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Gruen, Victor, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Highway lobby -- general, undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - House Appropriations Committee, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - House District Committee, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Justement, Louis, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - League of Women Voters, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - The Mansfield Bill, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - National Capital Parks, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - National Capital Planning Commission, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - National Capital Transportation Agency, undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - National Capital Transportation Agency, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - New Orleans, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, Vol. 1, 1960; Series 2 (Box 20, Binder 1)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, 1960; Series 2 (Box 12, Binder 1)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning -- National Capital Transportation Act of 1960, Series 2 (Box 12, Binder 2)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, Vol. 2, 1960; Series 2 (Box 21, Binder 1)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, Vol. 1, 1961 (Box 21, Binder 2)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, 1961; Series 2 (Box 12, Binder 3)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, Vol. 1, 1962 (Box 21, Binder 3)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, 1963; Series 2 (Box 12, Binder 4)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, Vol. 1, 1963; Series 1 (Box 16, Binder 6)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, Vol. 1, 1964; Series 2 (Box 20, Binder 2)
  - Northwest Committee for Transportation Planning, Vol. 1, 1965-1966; Series 2 (Box 20, Binder 3)
  - Potomac River power project, 1927-1928; Series 2 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Press, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Radio -- TV stations, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Republican State Committee -- DC, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Route 70-S Hearings Senate Public Works Committee, 1960; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Senate Appropriations Committee, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Senate District Committee, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Talks to Civic Groups, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Transportation Planning Board, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Urban League, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Virginia, state of, undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Commission, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - Washington Planning and Housing Association, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Washington Planning and Housing Association, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Washington Planning and Housing Association Transportation Committee, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - White House -- Mr. Horsky, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Wisconsin Avenue Committee for Transportation Problems, undated; Series 2 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Wisconsin corridor / Insterstate 70-S / Route 240 / Northwest Freeway, undated; Series 2 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Legal cases, 1963-1978; Series 3; 10 Linear Feet
  This series contains documents from lawsuits in which Peter S. Craig served as counsel on behalf of several different citizen and neighborhood associations. It also contains copies of public laws relating to transportation issues. These include seminal lawsuits like D.C. Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. v. Airis and D.C. Federation of Civic Associations v. Volpe, which were ultimately victories for Craig and his fellow lawyers over business and government interests attempting to build freeways through Washington, D.C. The material dates from 1963 to 1978, though some of the copies of public laws date to 1930.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - American University Park Citizens Association v. DC Council, 1972-1973; Series 3 (Box 37, Binder 9)
  - American University Park Citizens Association v. Burka, 1977; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - American University Park Citizens Association v. Burka, 1977; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Arlington Coalition on Transportation v. Volpe, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Binder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Restoration Society v. District of Columbia Zoning Commission, 1978; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Chevy Chase Citizens Association v. D.C. Council [1 of 3], 1972-1973; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Chevy Chase Citizens Association v. D.C. Council [2 of 3], 1972-1973; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Chevy Chase Citizens Association v. D.C. Council [3 of 3], 1972-1973; Series 3 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Chevy Chase Citizens Association v. D.C. Council, 1972; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Zoning Commission, 1972; Series 3 (Box 37, Binder 1)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Zoning Commission Decisions and Supplementary Memos, 1973; Series 3 (Box 15, Binder 3)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Zoning Commission [1 of 4], 1972; Series 3 (Box 16, Binder 1)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Zoning Commission [2 of 4], 1972; Series 3 (Box 16, Binder 2)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Zoning Commission [3 of 4], 1972; Series 3 (Box 16, Binder 3)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Zoning Commission [4 of 4], 1972; Series 3 (Box 16, Binder 4)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Walter E. Washington (Clean Air Act), 1973; Series 3 (Box 16, Binder 5)
  - Citizens Association of Georgetown v. Zoning Commission of the District of Columbia, 1978; Series 3 (Box 72, Binder 1)
  - Citizens for City Living, 1973; Series 3 (Box 29, Binder 1)
  - Citizens for City Living v. DC Zoning Commission, 1972; Series 3 (Box 34, Binder 5)
  - Committee of 100, 1973-1976; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Committee of 100, 1970-1973; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Committee of 100, 1963-1972; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - County Board of Arlington v. Hartzog, undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Binder 4)
  - DC Administrative Procedure Act and zoning cases, 1972-1974; Series 3 (Box 37, Binder 5)
  - DC cases, 1896-1962; Series 3 (Box 29, Binder 7)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. v. Thomas F. Airis [Airis case], undated; Series 3 (Box 47, Binder 1)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. v. Thomas F. Airis [Airis case, Vol. 2], 1967-1968; series 3 (Box 25, Binder 7)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. v. Thomas F. Airis [Airis case, Vol. 3], 1967-1968; series 3 (Box 25, Binder 8)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. v. Thomas F. Airis [Airis case, Vol. 4], 1967-1968; series 3 (Box 25, Binder 9)
  - Airis case, Joint Appendix [DC Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. v. Thomas F. Airis], 1967; Series 3 (Box 62, Volume 1)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations v. Volpe, undated; Series 3 (Box 29, Binder 9)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations v. Volpe, 1971; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations v. Volpe, 1972; Series 3 (Box 26, Binder 6)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations v. Volpe (attorney's fees), 1974-1977; series 3 (Box 15, Binder 5)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations, Inc. v. Volpe [Volpe Case Vol. 1], 1970; Series 3 (Box 26, Binder 7)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations v. Volpe [Volpe case briefs to Court of Appeal], undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Binder 5)
  - DC Federation of Civic Associations v. Volpe [Volpe case briefs and decisions on second appeal], 1971-1972; series 3 (Box 15, Binder 6)
  - Duke deposition January 3, 1967, 1967 January 03; Series 3 (Box 47, Binder 2)
  - Freeway lawsuits pleadings, undated; Series 3 (Box 35, Binder 1)
  - Georgetown Waterfront Rezoning, 1972; Series 3 (Box 37, Binder 2)
  - Georgetown Waterfront Rezoning, 1973; Series 3 (Box 37, Binder 3)
  - Georgetown Zoning, 1972-1973; Series 3 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Georgetown Zoning Litigation, 1973-1975; Series 3 (Box 15, Binder 4)
  - Graham Building Associates [proposed development of Square 1045 on Capitol Hill], 1974; Series 3 (Box 37, Binder 7)
  - Legal cases, 1970-1975; Series 3 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - McLean Gardens NCPC Hearing, 1973 January 04; series 3 (Box 16, Binder 7)
  - McLean Gardens Residents Association v. NCPC, Volume 1, 1972; Series 3 (Box 18, Binder 3)
  - McLean Gardens Residents Association v. NCPC, Volume 2, 1972; Series 3 (Box 17, Binder 1)
  - McLean Gardens Residents Association v. NCPC and Zoning Commission, 1973; Series 3 (Box 17, Binder 3)
  - McLean Gardens Rezoning -- Citizens for City Living, 1972-1973; Series 3 (Box 17, Binder 2)
  - McLean Gardens Rezoning -- Traffic Impact, 1969-1971; Series 3 (Box 18, Binder 1)
  - McLean Gardens Rezoning -- Docket and Briefs, 1970-1971; Series 3 (Box 18, Binder 2)
  - Public laws, 1930-1936; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Public laws, 1930-1946; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Public laws, 1937-1940; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Public laws, 1941-1946; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Public laws, 1947-1954; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Public laws, 1955-1962; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Public laws, 1963-1965; Series 3 (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Clippings, 1911-1980; Series 4; 10 Linear Feet
  This series contains newspaper clippings gathered by Peter S. Craig as part of his legal work in opposition to freeway construction in Washington, D.C. The material dates from 1911 to 1980 and includes some historical materials that far predate Craig's work. The clippings document the controversies surrounding many proposed transportation projects and the roles played by civic organizations as well as local and national government.
  Arranged alphabetically, beginning first with general files marked "Clippings" and continuing with files of clippings on specific subjects or locations.
  - Clippings, 1926-1929; Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1945-1948; Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1958; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 9)
  - Clippings, 1959; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 1)
  - Clippings, 1960 January-May; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 2)
  - Clippings, 1960 May-June; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 3)
  - Clippings, 1960 July-September; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 4)
  - Clippings, 1960 October-December; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 5)
  - Clippings, 1961 January-March; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 6)
  - Clippings, 1961 April-June; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 7)
  - Clippings, 1961 July-September; Series 4 (Box 44, Binder 8)
  - Clippings, 1961 October-November; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 1)
  - Clippings, 1961 November-December; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 2)
  - Clippings, 1962 January-March; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 3)
  - Clippings, 1962 April-June; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 4)
  - Clippings, 1962 June-July; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 5)
  - Clippings, 1962 August-September; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 6)
  - Clippings, 1962 October-December; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 8)
  - Clippings, 1963 January-March; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 9)
  - Clippings, 1963 April-July; Series 4 (Box 43, Binder 7)
  - Clippings, 1963 July-September; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 1)
  - Clippings, 1963 October-November; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 3)
  - Clippings, 1963 November-December; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 2)
  - Clippings, 1964 January-March; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 6)
  - Clippings, 1964 April-June; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 4)
  - Clippings, 1964 July-September; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 5)
  - Clippings, 1964 October-December; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 7)
  - Clippings, 1960-1964; Series 4 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1965 January-March; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 8)
  - Clippings, 1965 April-June; Series 4 (Box 38, Binder 9)
  - Clippings, 1965 July-September; Series 4 (Box 6, Binder 1)
  - Clippings, 1965 October-December; Series 4 (Box 6, Binder 2)
  - Clippings, 1966 January-March; Series 4 (Box 6, Binder 3)
  - Clippings, 1966 April-June; Series 4 (Box 6, Binder 4)
  - Clippings, 1966 July-September; Series 4 (Box 6, Binder 5)
  - Clippings, 1966 October-December; Series 4 (Box 6, Binder 6)
  - Clippings, 1967 January-March; Series 4 (Box 6, Binder 7)
  - Clippings, 1967 April; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1967 May; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1967 June; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1967 July; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1967 August; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1967 September; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1967 October; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1967 November; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1967 December; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1968 January; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1968 February; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1968 March; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1968 April; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1968 May; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1968 June; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1968 July; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1968 August; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1968 September; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1968 October; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1968 November; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1968 December; Series 4 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1969 January; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1969 February; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1969 March; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, 1969 April; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Clippings, 1969 May; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Clippings, 1969 June; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Clippings, 1969 July; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1969 August; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1969 September; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1969 October; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1969 November; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1969 December; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1970 January; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Clippings, 1970 February; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Clippings, 1970 March; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Clippings, 1970 April; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Clippings, 1970 May; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, 1970 June; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Clippings, 1970 July; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1970 August; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Clippings, 1970 September; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Clippings, 1970 October; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1970 November; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Clippings, 1970 December; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, 1971 January; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Clippings, 1971 February; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Clippings, 1971 March; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Clippings, 1971 April; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Clippings, 1971 May; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Clippings, 1971 June; Series 4 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Clippings, 1971 July; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Clippings, 1971 August; Series 4 (Box 53, Folder 26)